# FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT **DEVELOPER**

# JEANPIERRE ECHEVARRIA CASTRO



#### **PROFILE**

I am Fullstack Javascript Developer with four years of experience in the field of technology and one year of experience as a web developer. I want to collaborate in teams passionate about developing digital products with technologies such as Node, React and other of my skills

## SOFT SKILL

- Verbal communication
- Empathy
- Active listening
- Collaboration
- Teamwork

# **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

2012 - 2015 Superior technology CIMA'S Computing and Information

2017 **UTP University** Systems engineer

2021 - 2022 Platzy.com

Certified Course in Node.js Certified Course in React.js Certificate Course in Web Development

## CONTACT DETAILS

Jeanpiereche@gmail.com



+51 986 705 000



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeanpiereche/



Lima, Perú

## WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2022

Telectronic Perú SAC

Support analyst

- Management and administration of the Verint CC platform for Movistar, Interbank, BCP and BBVA.
- Resolution of high and low impact incidents
- Generation of report through the Database

2015 - 2016 Soltronica SAC

Web Developer Jr

- Development of web pages.
- Development of mobile applications for Android.
- Maintenance of administrative portals (CMS).

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- Node JS
- MySql

- CSS
- Express API Rest
- SQL Server
- React PHP